PATRICIA DERIEUX

Phone: 832-525-3582 | Email: patricia.derieux15@outlook.com | The Woodlands, TX 77382 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/patricia-derieux | GitHub: https://github.com/patty345| Portfolio: https://patty345.github.io/advance-css-professional-portfolio/

SUMMARY

A self-motivated Front-end Web Developer with IT experience ready to make an impact in the field. Brining 7 years of work experience in IT as an Application Analyst where I have learned to be communicative, self-motivated, team-oriented, and problem-solver.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps, Heroku, VS Code, ServiceNow

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Application Analyst Perry Homes LLC

2018 - Current

Houston, TX

- Successfully reduced the user's communication method to our Sales staff when submitting exterior selections form.
- Improved team efficiency by using automation.
- Collaborated with a custom development team to improve exterior selections form, and received positive feedback from the stakeholders.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Support Specialist Perry Homes LLC

2014 - 2018

Houston, TX

- Supported the distribution and configuration of all employees IT equipment.
- Collaborated with my support team to accomplish the task at hand.
- Generated company efficiency by providing new equipment to all employees.

Advanced Repair Agent Best Buy

2013 - 2014

Webster, TX

- Resolved customers' computer problems.
 - Providing technical support, and repair services.
 - Delivering great customer services as well as repairing computer problems.

PROJECTS

Park Finder https://github.com/patty345 https://patty345.github.io/park-finder/

- An easy way to find parks near you.
- Developer, and scrum meetings coordinator
- VS Code / HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Foundation, jQuery, MapQuest, and Open Weather API

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development - Rice University

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, & ReactJS.

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems - University of Houston Houston, TX